

Serbia

% 065-208-35-37

www.jovand3v.com

jovand3v

in jovanilic23

SUMMARY

Hi, my name is Jovan Ilić. I'm a front-end developer from Serbia with back-end experience and a passion for design. I have been into web development, particularly React, for 5 years now. I consistently strive to write clean, reusable, well-documented, and optimized code, while actively seeking opportunities to enhance my skills and introduce innovative solutions to the projects I work on.

SKILLS LANGUAGES

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, TypeScript, Next.js, Node.js, Express, RESTful APIs, Figma, Netlify.

Serbian - Native English - Fluent

WORK EXPERIENCE

JAN 2021 - MAR 2022

Freelance

Fiverr and Private Clients - Front-end Developer(React, SCSS, Figma, Netlify)

Freelanced on Fiver and for Private Clients making various websites.

MAR 2022 - NOV 2022

MASHDAPP

Nephalum Ltd. - Full-stack Developer (React, TypeScript, SCSS, Mailgun, Figma, Netlify)

- Developed the entire responsive front-end, including a completely custom Editor and UI for customizing/combining NFTs.
- Developed a custom wallet system, using browser's wallet extensions, for connecting and displaying NFTs in a unique way, with custom options such as NFT video sequencing.
- · Handled hosting as well as smaller parts of back-end such as the contact form.
- Worked with the back-end developer to fully connect and test the front-end with the back-end.
- Researched about Cardano and gave an optimal solution to our back-end developer for storing large NFT images to the Blockchain.
- Designed 80% of the website.

AUG 2023 - PRESENT

Omura www.omura.finance

Nephalum Ltd. - Front-end Developer(Next.js, TypeScript, SCSS, TradingView, Figma, Vercel)

- Developed the entire front-end for a trading platform with its own marketplace, trade page, and dashboard using popular technologies.
- Communicated with the back-end developer to come up with the most optimal solutions for manipulating large datasets.
- Handled hosting.
- Worked with the back-end developer to fully connect and test the front-end with the back-end.
- Communicated with the designer, when needed, to provide optimal UI and UX.
- · Applied good SEO practices resulting in improved user engagement.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

2023 PHERRA www.pherra.vercel.app www.github.com/jovand3v/PHERRA

PHERRA is a personal full-stack, e-commerce project with a custom built cms. PHERRA is hosted on Vercel and was built using: Next.js, TypeScript, SCSS, JWT, Prisma, Vercel Postgres Database, AWS S3 Bucket, and Figma.

2021 Keep-Track <u>www.keep-track.netlify.app</u> <u>www.github.com/jovand3v/KeepTrack</u>

KEEPTRACK is a personal front-end, nutrition tracking project. It's hosted on Netlify and was built using: React, Redux, SCSS, chart.js, and Figma. This project was initially built for personal use only but later I've decided to re-design it, brand it, and put it as one of my projects even if it was built in 2021.

EDUCATION